{
  "name": "",
  "isFavorite": false,
  "cards": [
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Dog",
      "back": "Köpek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cat",
      "back": "Kedi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bird",
      "back": "Kuş"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Fish",
      "back": "Balık"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Horse",
      "back": "At"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Cow",
      "back": "İnek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Sheep",
      "back": "Koyun"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Goat",
      "back": "Keçi"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Pig",
      "back": "Domuz"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Chicken",
      "back": "Tavuk"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Duck",
      "back": "Ördek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rabbit",
      "back": "Tavşan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Frog",
      "back": "Kurbağa"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Elephant",
      "back": "Fil"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Lion",
      "back": "Aslan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Tiger",
      "back": "Kaplan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bear",
      "back": "Ayı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Wolf",
      "back": "Kurt"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Fox",
      "back": "Tilki"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Monkey",
      "back": "Maymun"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Giraffe",
      "back": "Zürafa"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Zebra",
      "back": "Zebra"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Kangaroo",
      "back": "Kanguru"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Crocodile",
      "back": "Timsah"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Snake",
      "back": "Yılan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Turtle",
      "back": "Kaplumbağa"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Insect",
      "back": "Böcek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Ant",
      "back": "Karınca"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bee",
      "back": "Arı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Butterfly",
      "back": "Kelebek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Spider",
      "back": "Örümcek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Fly",
      "back": "Sinek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Bat",
      "back": "Yarasa"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Mouse",
      "back": "Fare"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Rat",
      "back": "Sıçan"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Owl",
      "back": "Baykuş"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Peacock",
      "back": "Tavus kuşu"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Penguin",
      "back": "Penguen"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Seal",
      "back": "Fok balığı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Whale",
      "back": "Balina"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Dolphin",
      "back": "Yunus"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Shark",
      "back": "Köpekbalığı"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Octopus",
      "back": "Ahtapot"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Crab",
      "back": "Yengeç"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Lizard",
      "back": "Kertenkele"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Camel",
      "back": "Deve"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Donkey",
      "back": "Eşek"
    },
    {
      "level": 0,
      "front": "Turkey",
      "back": "Hindi"
    }
  ]
}
